Alicia: Hello, I’m Alicia. Today I’m in Brighton. Brighton is in the south of England.
It’s on the coast. It’s a fantastic town, and it’s famous for the Royal Pavilion, the pier, and the beach.
But I’m not on holiday. I’m here to visit an English language school.
This is the school. It’s a big school with about three hundred and fifty students.
Rike and Woo are students at the school. Hyeongwoo is twenty-three years old.
He’s from Korea. He’s a beginner student. His class is small, with only five students.
His teacher is Stephen. He’s English. He’s very friendly, and he’s a very good teacher.
Rike is nineteen years old. She’s from Germany.
She’s an intermediate student, and her class is big, with eleven students. Her teacher is Laura.
She’s English. She’s really nice, and she’s a very good teacher, too.
When Rike and Woo aren’t in class, they’re in the computer room…or here, in the canteen.
In the evening they’re at home. Rike and Woo live in a student house. It’s near the school.
It’s a big house with five bedrooms, a kitchen, and a garden.
Brighton is great for students like Rike and Hyeongwoo.
The people are friendly, and the town is exciting and fun!